serious illnesses like heart diseases
and cancer are now a bigger threat than
ever before
stressful lifestyles poor food habits
and increasing pollution may put you at
a greater risk of getting heart diseases
or cancer
[Music]
but do you think these illnesses will
affect just your health
well think again
in most cases heart diseases and cancer
require urgent treatments which means a
sudden need for a large sum of money
to arrange for this sum your family may
have to break the savings that you had
kept aside to fulfill future aspirations
then how can you get the best treatment
without causing a strain on your family
and future plans presenting icici pro
heart and cancer protect a specially
designed health insurance plan that
covers both heart diseases and cancer a
plan that pays your claim amount up
front on the first diagnosis of the
covered heart diseases and cancers
with this lump sum money in your hand
you can get the best treatment
immediately so no need to worry about
medical bills or filing reimbursement
claims or finding an approved hospital
and above all for a premium amount of
just rupees 100 per month you can get a
large cover of rupees 17.8 lakhs
so you can now focus on your speedy
recovery
with icici proof heart and cancer
protect
[Music]